When you sell in the Amazon store,
you must comply with all applicable laws
as well as Amazon's policies.
Our policies are in place for the protection
of both our customers and sellers.
Let's take a quick look at a few of those policies,
product condition, authenticity, customer reviews,
and listing policies.
Ensure that your product listings follow our requirements
and that the products your customers receive
match the listing information on the product detail pages.
These policies help us provide customers
with the best possible experience
when they shop in the Amazon store.
Our product safety and restricted products policies
ensure that products are safe for customers
and that they comply with all legal regulations.
When we identify products with a high safety risk,
we either restrict the sale of the product
or take extra precautions to ensure the product is safe.
The Amazon Intellectual Property Policy
protects the rights of intellectual property owners,
products listed in the Amazon store,
must not infringe on the rights of intellectual property owners,
including copyrights, patents, and trademarks.
These are just a few of the selling policies
you will encounter as an Amazon seller.
You can find details about all of our selling policies
by searching for selling policies
and seller code of conduct in Seller Central.
Sellers who don't comply with our policies
will be notified on the account health dashboard,
which you can find by clicking on your account health rating
from the Seller Central home page.
Failure to comply with any of our selling policies
may impact your ability to sell in the Amazon store.